Yo!
THE DAY OF THE SPORTS FESTIVAL 6:30 AM
Hey, good morning!
- Hey, good morning!
- Hey, lil Tsukko.
- What's wrong?
- Oh.
Well...
I got kinda caught up in the moment when
I joined the cheer squad.
And ever since I've been nervous
that I'll mess up the choreography.
And then I'm worried whether
someone like me from a cultural club
would be accepted attempting to
cheer people on, even though I'm
not an athlete.
All of it just makes me so anxious.
No, everyone's gonna love you, so
let's cheer our hearts out!
I get it.
Could you maybe help her with that?
Help her with that?
Well, Momoka's probably not a bad person.
And it's not like I'm gonna try to
make anything happen with Amamiya.
I mean...
She seems like she's nice to everyone.
So I guess her being nice to me
isn't that weird.
She doesn't know how I feel and,
honestly, no one else needs to either.
So it's not like-
Don't overthink it...
Don't overthink it.
Act normal...
THE RAMPARTS OF ICE
Perception
THE DAY OF THE SPORTS FESTIVAL 7:00 AM
FINAL MORNING PRACTICE
We're gonna go out there and kick their
butts!
Yeah!
8:00 AM GIRLS' HAIR SETTING
We have a ton of blue accessories so
whoever wants to put them in their hair,
just grab some, okay?
Hey, Yota?
THE SHORT-HAIRED CREW WITH NOTHING TO DO
- How nuts?
- It won't look all weird?
It'll be fine. Don't worry!
Just trust me!
8:20 AM
Whoa!
Everyone's hair is so impressive!
- Wow!
- You look great too!
Lemme do your hair for you!
Koyun. This is quite a look.
Apparently, it's "onion hair."
Oh no, Yota stop it.
What? This is an onion?
If Amamiya sees it...
Oh, Jeez. Too late.
Uh, what's going on with Miki?
Huh?
SNAP
- Uh!
- Uh! Oh.
You look good.
Huh?
All three of you do.
SPORTS FESTIVAL
MORNING SEGMENT
Let's go!
Yota! Minato!
Gah! It's super high up!
It's low-key scary!
She looks adorable, like a
little hamster.
Ah, so cute!
OBSTACLE RACE
- Glide.
- Get a move on!
Go!
Glide.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go,
GIRLS' POLE PULL
let's go!
- Yeah!
- Oh, Miki.
PLOP PLOP
Humiliating.
There, there.
CLUB COMPETITION RELAY RACE
Whoa! What's up with you, Minato? Dang.
Let's get a photo.
Man, the costume gets me even more
into it!
Right?
The pants Miki sewed for me work
perfectly.
- Wow, my gosh, you all look so cool!
- Hm?
Hey, Momoka.
That's a really good look for you.
And for you too!
I never see you with your hair up.
Cute right? A third-year did it for me.
- So cute!
- You are too. It looks amazing!
Huh?
CHITTER-CHATTER
- When did they get so close?
- It gives a different vibe.
- You think so?
- Tsukiko, you look totally adorable!
You think so?
What? What?! No way.
I'm humbled to be told that by
someone like you. I mean, you would
know about cute, right?
Oh. What do I do?
- Huh?
- Hey, I'll come with you.
- That's okay!
- This is bad. What do I do?
Oh, no.
I just had a really dark feeling come up.
Whoa!
Koyun.
We seem to run into each other a lot.
Sorry. I'll pay better attention.
Uh.
Hey, Yota?
Hayato's over there and-
Huh?
SNATCH! GASP!
Uh, no. It's not...
It's not what?
What do I do?
Uh. I...
I gotta get back to Miki and the
others. Bye!
PANTING
What was that?
What in the world am I doing?
Koyun?
AFTERNOON CHEER BATTLE SEGMENT
Hah!
So cool!
EACH TEAM FINISHED WITHOUT A HITCH
PHOTO-TAKING TIME
(THE POINTS ARE BEING TALLIED)
- Wow, thank you so much!
Like from a boy band.
I'm gonna blow this picture up, turn it
into a poster and hang it in my room!
My life span just increased by a hundred
years!
Ah, the energy of youth.
A photo.
- No, no.
- Hey there, Amamiya!
Let's take a selfie together, okay?
Uh. Sure.
Just like that.
I need to ask Koyun directly, like she
just did.
But right now, I'm way too scared.
I got separated from everyone.
Did they already go back to the
changing room?
Oh!
- Madam Koyun!
- Huh!
BOUNCE BOUNCE I'M BEING BECKONED...
Quick, get in here.
Let's take a group selfie.
WALKING
I feel like I'd be in the way.
Ugh. That'd be so awkward.
Here. Could you please take a photo of us?
Uh.
Sure.
Uhh...
Hold on, what kind of face is that?
Thank you so much!
Now one of just us. Say cheese!
That was awesome! See you later!
I was definitely making a weird face
in that picture.
Let's take a photo over there!
Yeah, let's go!
But edit it before posting.
- A photo...
Let's take one together.
If I was gonna say it...
- Now would definitely be the moment, but...
IT'D BE OUT OF CHARACTER
My brain keeps coming up with all
these negative thoughts.
WILL MY FEELINGS BE EXPOSED?
Stare.
- Ah!
- Huh?
All right. Moment immortalized.
Come on.
The soccer club's gathering.
Move it along!
Wait, wait, wait a minute!
No, take it properly.
Make sure it looks good.
You diva.
Wanna strike a pose?
Huh? Um, I...
FLUSTER
- Uh. Mm.
- Mm. Uh.
Hm? Hey.
I'm taking it.
Yo, Minato!
Kenta was just asking for you.
Oh.
Thanks! Coming!
FWUMP
So is the soccer club always that
casual with each other or is it-
Hey, Koyun.
Is there anything you wanted to tell me?
GRIN
- Hmm?
- What?
- Fade...
- Hey.
Stop it.
I don't think I'm keeping anything
from you.
Really?
Huh...
I'm just saying, you have a habit of
keeping things from me.
WAIT, IT WAS YOUR BIRTHDAY?!
YOU SHOULD'VE TOLD US.
Like not telling me it was your birthday.
To be honest, it makes me feel a little
sad.
GLANCE
I wasn't hiding it.
It's more like.
I just-
I only just realized it myself.
Yeah.
And it really might only be all
in my head.
I'm so confused and...
I don't know.
Huh.
So I...
I didn't think it was worth sharing with
anyone else.
Or not yet anyway.
Well, you know, even if it's just a hazy
thing you're not quite sure what
it is yet, wouldn't you feel better
if you at least got it off your chest?
I know I definitely felt better
after sharing what I was feeling with
- you.
- Hm.
Yota.
- Mm?
- Shuffle, shuffle, shuffle.
- CLICK CLATTER
- Come, come.
Hm? Scuffle, scuffle, scuffle, scuffle.
LOOKS AROUND
The thing is, I think I...
Hmm.
I see.
Koyun, you have surprisingly bad taste.
But still, he looks pretty happy
while saying that, doesn't he?
I see.
So we're feeling the same thing.
To be honest...
- Huh?
- He wasn't my cup of tea.
In fact, I was even scared of him.
That's how I used to feel, but...
Well I... I don't know why.
Things just changed over time.
I know this sounds weird, but I can't
explain how or when it happened or
what I feel.
Hey, welcome to the club.
Mm.
I can help you get some alone time
with him?
No! Don't you even dare!
Oh.
DOING IT
Sorry about that.
HAHA
Just know...
I don't wanna take things further or
change it from how we are now.
All of us hanging out together.
Me and him enjoying each other's
friendship.
I feel like that's more than enough for
me.
I'm really comfortable with exactly
where we are.
I'd hate to screw it up.
We're both in the same boat.
Hmm.
Oh no, I wonder if someday my
heart will be filled with soot too
- or something.
- We'll be twins.
No thanks.
Alright everyone, the points have all
been tallied up!
The closing ceremony will now begin.
Please make your way to the schoolyard.
I hate to say it, but if it's
Minato we're talking about,
it'll be hard.
Yeah.
I kind of figured that would be the case.
Hey!
FOUND YOU!
- Koyun! Yota. I found you!
- Hm?
- Huh?
- Oh.
I'm so glad I finally found you guys!
The four of us haven't taken a photo
together yet.
What do I do?
Maybe it's 'cause I just opened up, but I
feel super self-conscious right now.
Hm?
Were Yota and Koyun alone together
this whole time?
Were the two of them alone together
GLANCE, GLANCE
Don't look my way.
Same to you.
HAHA HEE-HEE-HEE...
- Uh.
The way we are right now is how I
want it to stay.
GAPING
I don't wanna ruin it.
This thing we have.
Selfie time!
Everyone, scoot in!
CLICK
If I had one wish, I'd wish we could
keep this peace and happiness forever.
GRADE 2 CLASS 2
That was awesome, it was so great!
Man, the sports festival was so much more
fun than last year's.
It really was.
NOISY
I was honestly nervous about cheer
squad, but it ended up being super fun.
Right?
LAST YEAR'S SPORTS FESTIVAL...
A CLASS WITH ZERO UNITY
Well, I guess how much fun you have
depends on who you do it with.
I was thinking the same thing,
but decided not to say it.
By the way, where's Miki?
GRADE 2 CLASS 2 SPORTS COMMITTEE
She has clean-up duties for sports
committee.
HEEHEE...
You got this, Yota.
Alright!
Let's go karaoke our little butts off!
- Man, I'm starving.
- I'm gonna order a boatload of fries.
- Yeah!
- Should we wait for Yota?
- Okay.
- Boys have so much energy.
They really do.
Huh?
- Oh!
- What's up?
We made eye contact.
You waiting for Miki?
Mm-mm. We were about to head home.
She told us not to wait up for her.
Gotcha.
Well, see you, Amamiya.
Nice work today.
- Uh!
- Let's head home, Tsukiko.
Huh? No, really?
She's gonna cut it short?
I'm sure Amamiya must've wanted to
chat a bit longer.
Then again, it's not like I'm gonna do
anything about it.
Oh.
The photos I took today.
I'll text 'em to you.
She's contacting me later!
Good for you, Amamiya!
Hey. Hold on!
Th- The after-party on Saturday.
Are you gonna be there?
- Huh?
- Hm?
After-party?
The cheer squad after-party?
We're getting yakiniku!
- Huh?
- Hadn't heard of it.
They just sent a message to the blue
squad group chat.
They're trying to get a headcount for it.
Oh. Guess you're right.
I had my notifications turned off.
Me too.
But why would you turn your notifications
off?
- Cause there's too many of 'em.
How goes it, Amamiya?
What are you guys doing?
Oh, Hayato.
You're always hanging around as if you
actually belong in this class.
What's up? What's this about?
The party.
- You goin'?
- Mmm.
I work my part-time job Saturday, so
I'm not sure if I can.
Oh, what time?
From eleven a.m., 'til three p.m.
Oh well, we're not meeting 'til six.
You'll totally make it.
You're not going, Hikawa?
What? Why not?
It'll be more fun if we're all there!
Bro, go back to your class.
Come on, let's go!
- That makes me so sad.
- It's not Class Two if we're not all
- there, right?
- Uh?
Huh?
NOD
I think...
- We'll go.
- See ya.
See you tomorrow.
Other scare me.
- It freaks me out.
- Oh no, I said that we'd go!
You did say that.
I can see it now.
Me sitting in the corner of
the restaurant, unable to keep up
with the vibe. What do I do?
We'll just sit next to each other.
Well...
The sports festival came and went
quickly this year.
It did.
It's a bummer that we won't have cheer
squad practice any more, right?
But I'm excited for the after-party.
Right?
SUPPLY ROOM
You know I love a good after- party, but
I'm more looking forward to our next
group hang. What should we do next time?
The Uppi park again?
They may offer different events depending
on the season we're in.
The four seasons of Uppi.
I kinda wanna see that.
That's hilarious.
Oh.
Hey, just so you know, I haven't
forgotten about our plans for
the two of us to hang one-on-one.
So you better not forget either.
Of course no-
Let's go everywhere.
Miki!
Ugh! Ooh!
Yeah. Ow.
Yota? Are you alright?
Whoa! Sorry! No, it's not-
Er, i-it fell and I-
Oh, uh, I know.
And I appreciate it.
Did you get hit on the forehead?
Are you feeling okay?
Uh. Uh! Hey!
- Yeah, no, I'm fine!
- Huh?
Uhh.
Hey, what's the matter with you?
Why're you being shy?
We've known each other forever.
Don't suddenly get all weird on me 'cause
I'm a girl.
That's not it.
It's not just that you're a girl.
To me, you're Miki.
You're not just some girl.
Huh?
What is he saying?
Yeah, there's not doubt about it.
You know no one else can be me but me!
Hm?
I'm just glad that the box wasn't full
of heavy stuff.
For sure.
How does it feel where it hit you?
- Where was it again?
- I'm fine.
Don't worry.
I'm confused. What was that?
It felt like-
I'll help.
Hm?
No way.
It can't be.
No, that's not possible.
I mean, it's me we're talking about.
There's no way he'd see me like that.
SWIFT
Uh. Okay.
There you go!
- Huh?
- All done!
We're outta here!
Locking up!
You know what? I gotta return the key.
Okay, anyway, see ya!
- Uh, Mi--
- That was fast.
Miki.
If...
If Yota's feelings really are
what I think they are...
How long has he felt this way?
All this time...
CLICK-CLICK-CLICK-CLICK-CLICK
SWIFT MOVEMENTS
I thought we were friends.
What do I do?
If the entire time I've known you, I
thought our relationship was one
thing, when actually it was something
very different.
I love you.
Mm.
I love you, too.
What do I do?
All the memories we made...
The things he said to me...
All his kindness...
Take on a different meaning now.